SKILLS

Git

Next.js

React.js

WordPress

Tailwind CSS

HTML - CSS - JavaScript

CONTACT

Phone +58 412 7641520

E-mail <u>carlosmrtzodev@gmail.com</u>

GitHub https://github.com/carlosmrtzodev

Portfolio Carlos Martínez

Featured project <u>Pokédex App</u>

CARLOS MARTÍNEZ FRONT END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

My goal is to create cool looking websites and interfaces.

With a trajectory of a few years from when I started with HTML/CSS/JavaScript to working with WordPress and currently specializing more with technologies such as React.js/Next.js/Tailwind CSS.

I'm passionate about creating things with a great style, I studied **Computer Engineering** because of my curiosity in computers and there I found the interest in **Web Development**, more precisely in the **Front End** area.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER (FREELANCE)

Remote Work Freelance | Sep 2020 - Currently

 Front End Development - WordPress - Elementor - HTML5 -CSS3 - JavaScript - React.js - Next.js - Tailwind CSS

WEB DEVELOPER

Atel Trading, C.A | Feb 2020 - Sep 2020

• Content Management System (CMS) - WordPress - Moodle.

FRONT END DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIPS)

SERVIEDUCA, C.A | Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

• Front End Developer - Angular - Node.js

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY STUDIES, COMPUTER ENGINEER

Dr. Rafael Belloso Chacin University | Jan 2016 - Nov 2019

WEB MASTER, DIPLOMA

Dr. Rafael Belloso Chacin University | Jan 2019 - Aug 2019

REACT - DEFINITIVE GUIDE: HOOKS ROUTER REDUX NEXT + PROJECTS

Udemy, Jan 2022